Hello!

I'm Gideon Jones

Provo, UT 84606 **(801) 709-0023**

gideon.w.jones@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gideon-jones-9173081b2 Personal Projects: https://github.com/GideonJones999 School Projects: https://github.com/GideonJonesMTECH

Skills

I am a Programmer with experience in Javascript, C#, C++, React, Angular, and working well in a team! I'm currently a student at BYU studying Software Engineering, and I'm so

excited to get to learn more and grow in my abilities as a programmer and as a teammate.



Experience

August 2021 - August 2023

The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, Campinas Brazil- Full-Time Missionary

- I learned how to connect and relate with the people around me.
- I had the opportunity to lead the people on my team, working with goals and specific plans so we could have better results.
- I learned how to speak the Portuguese Language, and I still use it to communicate with those around me.

July 2021 - August 2021

Three Octaves - Extern

Jason Baddley - (801) 644-7540

- I learned how to work on a real project on a real team, participating in Standup Meetings, Kanban Planning, and more.
- I practiced a lot of front-end work, implementing the data given simply and easily for the consumer to understand.

Education

Present

BYU Provo - Freshman in the Software Engineering Major

I just started to study at BYU. I've been very grateful for the experience, and I've already learned a lot about hard work, and continuing to grow and learn.

2020 - 2021

Mountainland Technical College - Graduate of the Web Page, Digital/Multimedia, and Information Resources Design Program

I finished my studies in the Web Development Program of MTECH, which I loved. Through MTECH, I have become proficient in HTML, styling, Angular, React, quality assurance, and Javascript.

2017 - 2021

Lehi High School - *Graduate*

I graduated from Lehi High School with honors, having studied hard and developed the skills of working with instructors, applying the lessons I was learning, and working productively on projects.

Awards

July 2017

Eagle Scout

I got my Eagle Scout! It was a lot of hard work, but it was a joy to work on. For my project, I made 2 LEGO tables for Thunder Ridge Elementary, so kids with special needs could play with LEGOs. It was an amazing experience to give those to the kids, everyone seemed so thrilled to have them.